CRAIG PUTZSTUCK

P: 512.317.1374 | E: putzstuck@gmail.com | Port Richey, FL 34668

LinkedIn | GitHub | Portfolio

SUMMARY

Accomplished coding bootcamp graduate proficient in various JavaScript dialects, developing applications and creating MERN projects from the ground up. Expertly trained in MySQL, MongoDB, Express.js, Node.js and React.js. 5+ years of experience in logistics, scheduling, inventory management and interpersonal communication.

RELEVANT SKILLS

MongoDB	Third-Party API	HTML5	Bootstrap
MySQL	Express JS	CSS3	Handlebars JS
Mongoose JS	ООР	React	MVC Paradigm
iQuery	Server-Side API	JavaScript	Node JS

EXPERIENCE

WAREHOUSE MANAGER – *West Shore Home* – Tampa, Florida 2020 – 2022

- Predictively manage stock inventory levels and forecast upcoming events to prevent material shortages.
- Precisely receive product deliveries and quickly notify relevant parties of expedited or damaged product.

WAREHOUSE MANAGER – *Denver Hardwood* – Colorado Springs, Colorado 2017 – 2020

- Precisely controlled inventory through frequent cycle counts and subsequent adjustment.
- Critically review delivery schedules with other departments and the customer to ensure accuracy.

OFFICE ADMINISTRATOR – *American Trailer Sales* – Colorado Springs, Colorado 2012 – 2017

- Accurately managed inventory and processed customer special orders.
- Jointly oversaw bookkeeping, administrative duties and general office management.

PHOTOGRAPHER – *Bob Penkhus Volvo Mazda* – Colorado Springs, Colorado 2010 – 2012

- Expertly provide professional-grade staging, lighting and photography of used vehicles.
- Closely assist in the internet marketing of the used car division.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY of COLORADO

Colorado Springs, Colorado 2003 – 2005

UNIVERSITÄT LÜNEBURG

Lüneburg, Germany 2004

UNIVERSITY of CENTRAL FLORIDA

Orlando, Florida Full Stack Immersive 2022

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- 3rd Party API's
- Node JS, Express JS, React
- MySQL, MongoDB